I'm going to show John Kiryako is a former head of counterterrorism CIA in Afghanistan other countries.
Very famous, very prestigious, very documented, what he said was true, exposing illegal torture programs and more.
I've interviewed him a few times and he did a great job, but he has been on fire with Patrick Bed David and Tucker Carlson.
On Israel, really trying to take over the United States, not just foreign policy and so much more.
So very impressed and again, he's not anti-Israel folks.
And I want to be clear, I don't say that as like wink, wink, dog whistle, I love Hitler, you know, but oh, I don't really hate all the Jews.
It's just the Zionist crap.
I'm a somewhat of a historian and I've experienced a lot and Israel until recently was not the dominant lobbying force in the United States.
It was the Communist Chinese, the Black Rock Globalists and the rest of it.
But Israel really is because the Democrats are in such this array trying a hostile takeover of the White House and they basically have control of Middle Eastern foreign policy.
And so I legitimately am concerned by the moves Israel is making and the things they're doing because it is the most popular thing, the fastest growing thing.
The majority of people around the world, the majority of Democrats, like 90% of them, close to half of Republicans now hate Israel.
And see, I know how to think second, third, fourth, fifth order consequences.
Hey, I don't want the people in Israel to get blown up a nuclear war.
I don't hate them.
I don't like to corrupt people government.
And Israel is destroying itself in the world's eyes.
And then I understand Israel's got thousands of nuclear weapons, not hundreds and high tech delivery systems and the Samsung option.
People always go, God, they'll blow everybody up.
I think I'm blowing up.
That's called mad.
We got it too.
I'm just going to call things as they are the way he's defending Israel.
Now he's attacking Israel.
I just look at the issue was attacking the Liberty trying to sing it to blame Egypt where they'll be J nice.
No, that was horrible.
Incredible.
Oh my God, the Jews will if somebody nukes them, they'll nuke them in the world.
Samsung option.
We call it mad.
My brain only works on being informed and covering things as they are.
But the biggest enemy of Jews worldwide is Benjamin Netanyahu.
And you know, you heard Michael Savage on two weeks ago.
He's pro-Israel.
He's an American first guy.
He doesn't call himself a Zionist, but he's pro-Israel.
And I admire Michael because he's so articulate and so smart on so many fronts.
I mean, you know, and, and he said, no, I talked to top Israelis and top generals, all of them.
And they say Netanyahu is going to get Israel destroyed because they're smart.
They're not against Israel.
They're not even against Israel expanding, you know, but.
What did Savage say?
Take the foot off the gas?
Yeah.
If everybody that just says, you know, to the mountains of the sea, kill all the Jews.
You understand that means nuclear war, right?
Now I could hit a button right now and send all the Jews to Mars.
I wouldn't do it.
But at the same time, I am extremely sick of the ADL on the left and just my whole career on air being called anti-Semitic.
If I say there's globalist and there's a World Bank and the Federal Reserve is private.
Oh, that's a secret code word for Jews.
Well, I mean, the Rothschilds, when they set up the Federal Reserve was the only audit, owned something like 80% of the shares in it.
So yeah, Jews own the Federal Reserve.
Okay, you can't own something that's shadowy and basically runs things and then get mad if I say Jews control the Federal Reserve.
I mean, again, it's a fact.
So, and boy, if Trump was so controlled by the Jews, why won't they cut interest rates?
See, because the Jews aren't one block.
I mean, the grassroots Jews are basically, you know, a lot of them are leftists and some of them self-hating, but what you could say is upset about it.
It's kind of pejorative, but that's just the term I would use for everybody knows what that means.
I'm going off on a Jaguar on your calls, but in general, when Israel gets attacked or Jews are attacked,
almost all Jews line up together with solidarity to support the group.
That's completely natural, tribal, it's normal. It's a survival mechanism.
So yeah, Jews are one block when it kind of comes to Jews are being persecuted.
That's kind of why Israel starting in 47 started bombing Jews in Spain, Portugal, Syria and a bunch of other countries.
That's all declassified and blaming it on Muslims and on Nazis to make Jews move to Israel.
So the real relationship is the different kleptocratic Jewish mafias setting up Jews in Israel for calamity and then staying in power to do that.
And then scapegoating Jews in general by it because Jews are smart on average.
You know, they're not stupid, but when it comes to this, they've got a real blind spot.
Because I've sat there and explained this to prominent Jews off record and actually sold a bunch of them on it because they didn't know about it.
And then I've seen the Jews go out and act on what I've told them.
So it's not like they're just telling me what I want to hear. I see them change.
So, you know, I just I don't want to be in the position of having to roll up my sleeves and really go after Israel.
But man, Israel is going after our country and our sovereignty and has no right to run our country.
And that's where I stand on it. Let's go to your phone calls.
And then I'll get into the genius hack and all the rest of it's some really big threats to freedom.
But I mean, that's it. I legitimately care about everybody.
I legitimately want prosperity and peace. I legitimately want to live in peace.
And that's a whole other thing. I can't sit there and watch Israel be an ethno state and have rules on Jews can't marry non-Jews in Israel.
And I'm like, fine, you're allowed to have an ethno state. I'm not even saying people can't have that.
But but then if some white Christians just want to be white separatists and preserve their culture,
the ADL, the Jewish lobby and all of it attacks them and says they're Nazis.
Well, why do you get to have an ethno state and white people can't or black people go and try to create their own thing?
And you go, God, look at these racist black people over here. They're created their own, you know, community.
Well, you've done it. You got nuclear weapons. I mean, it's just like it's the logic of it.
Now there's been growing. So I just won't sit here and be lectured how I'm at all Hitler when it would take me 10 hours
to break down all the historical facts of the Jews feeding off the Jews in World War Two with deals with Hitler.
And of course, Hitler double crossed them all at the end. That's why Madeline Albright's dad, one of the main Jews,
running the operations of the Nazis, rounding up Jews. He was at the top, Soros was at the bottom.
You know, like people like Steve Puchenek, who's Jewish or half Jewish.
I guess the dad's Catholic, the mom is Jewish, so that makes him Jewish.
You know, high level CIA at the time, a long time ago, really smart guy.
But, you know, he would go off on it all day long about how the Jewish leadership made a deal with Hitler and all this
and knew about the persecution coming and had a deal with some of the Palestine.
But in the middle of it, the Germans lost control of North Africa and the Middle East.
And they said, no, you were just going to kill all of you now.
And then they, of course, rounded up. Even in Paris, one of the Rothschilds was running a bank with all the stolen Jew money
they took from their own people and they killed them.
So it's true, even a couple of Rothschilds got killed.
Oh, you mean Hitler double crossed you? Yeah.
You got out, criminal.
Rothschild, try this, try this game. Rothschild bad, Hitler bad.
See, you're not supposed to go Rothschild good, Hitler bad, or Hitler good, Rothschild bad.
No, Rothschild bad, Hitler bad. See how that works?
Sinai bad, arsenic bad. It's bad to be shot with a shotgun.
It's bad to be shot with some magnum in the head.
It's bad to have diesel port on you and it lit.
It's bad to have gasoline port on you and let's see everybody just thinks like there's two sides.
No, there's never just two sides, okay?
So yeah, am I worried about the, I mean, Soros is still alive and was helping round up Jews for the Nazis.
And I'm just like, because I know all about Hitler and don't compare me to you and your boss.
That's why the Nazis don't lie to me because they love Hugo Boss uniforms and the formations and the geometry and the architecture
and it makes them feel powerful to see a bunch of mainly homosexual men in black uniforms marching around.
Oh yeah, the Nazis were just coming up to me.
I just know too much. It's like Norris Barkley says, you know, I've gone crazy. I just know too much.
So no, I'm not a closeted anti-black person. I'm not a closeted anti-Hispanic. I'm not a closeted anti-Jew.
But what I am is openly against racist black people and that's not even most of them,
but they're out there and I will not bow to them and I won't bow to Jews trying to make me feel guilty to them.
And I'm not gonna bow to anybody and I'm proud to be white.
And there's only 7% of the world that's white and there's all these movements to not be white and don't have a white wife.
And I mean, hell, if you love some of this other color, I'm attracted to people of all colors.
But my point is, is it by always telling me it's bad that I'm white all day,
I'm like, well, I better get some more white babies around here.
Because I don't want the polar bears to go extinct.
And I'm sick of hearing about how white people are bad all day.
But just because I'm proud of myself and proud of my heritage doesn't mean that I don't like you because you're something else.
I can admire what your culture's done.
And anybody that says that Jews haven't produced a lot of science, music, literature, culture,
and there aren't some very highly performing Jews out there as a liar.
You know, the Nazis trying to, oh, there's not really highly, you know, Jews aren't as smart as...
Why does our whole religious world system come out of them?
I mean, just knock it off.
It is Judeo-Christian. Does it mean it's Jewish Christianity?
Now, that's what they mean. No, I mean, it comes out of Abraham.
Christianity came right out from between the legs of Abraham and the abomination of Islam.
And the Bible says this will be the abomination.
So just stop. We're obsessed with the Jews and they're obsessed with themselves because there is something special,
especially good and especially bad.
Because anything that's...
The more you can have a thousand horsepower car and you know how to drive it, it's great.
If you know how to drive it, you'll get your ass wrapped around a telephone pole.
And that's what I'm telling the Jews, not as one-month a group, but the ones...
You know who you are. Stop using psychological warfare.
Stop using black magic. Stop using dirty tricks.
Stop it because you don't think about black magic.
It comes back on the person that does it sevenfold.
You don't think...
Black magic, I mean in general, dirty tricks.
You don't think I'm not pretty smart and don't know how to do a lot of really nasty stuff to you after what you've done to me.
You don't think I don't know it's been your mafia that's been on top of my ass.
But I never took your bait, did you?
I warned you that you're going to get your asses in a lot of trouble where you're going.
And you're going to conjure a new Adolf Hitler.
It'll probably get us all killed.
See, I'm smart enough to look ahead here.
No, I'm actually Israel's best friend because I care about everybody.
And if you think, those of you that think you're going to blow the Jews up and they're not going to take you with them, you're an idiot.
But again, if I could blow the Jews up all right now and get away with it and I had a button, I wouldn't push it.
Because that's not in God's plan.
You start doing that. You know who's playing your part up.
You're like, oh wait, you're saying there with God? No.
There were the whole bunch of stuff.
When God favors you, so does the devil.
The more power I get, the more the devil comes knocking and more of the temptation gets.
So I know what the Jews have gone through because you know what? I'm exceptional. I'm powerful.
So I recognize you've had a lot of exception. I have exception.
And you know the Jewish lobby knows that about Northern Europeans and they don't like competition.
And that's why they're after them.
So stop it. You don't want people to war with you. Stop attacking us and we can figure out a future together.
Knock it off right now. I'm just talking straight to you.
People think they're going to kill the Jews and they're not going to blow everything up.
You think you're going to at the end of the day really bring down white Christian Western civilization
because the high IQs and the competition and you're threatened by it.
You think you don't think people don't see that.
You don't think you have it conjured something again now or you're going to get us all killed.
Nazis need to stop it. The out of control Jewish supremacy to stop it.
All you need to stop it.
Now that's straight shooting.
All right. Damn it. Let's go to phone calls. Excuse me. Matt in Ohio you're on the air. Go ahead.
I appreciate you. Everything you do. And I'll get straight to it. I know that's your preference.
We appreciate you brother. Go ahead.
But this whole roll up by Trump is so out of character from him.
Like where's his charisma is finger on the pulse and he's never on the wrong side of an 80-20 issue.
I like to use Occam's razor when I think about these kind of conspiratorial you know questions and make the least amount of assumptions.
I feel like the info isn't there or maybe the info will break down social order as we know it.
No one. No I mean that's it. I mean I mean he he got mad because he was snuck attack.
He's like yeah release it investigated. And then of course it's their foul.
He's like I'm in there. What the hell. A new rushing aid. And then he's just flips out about it.
And when we see it looking like a new Trump it said shock waves through people and we were right to say this is scary.
But I'm confirmed now he's starting to understand this and hopefully stops doing what he's been doing.
And then the special counsels coming. So that's good news.
I was going to say no one's talking about the intelligence side of this.
The FBI controls the criminal side and has the files on the criminal side.
The intelligence. If not us Israel as well.
And no one's talking about getting Tulsi and Radcliffe involved and to see their files on Epstein.
Also what if it's a lot scarier than you know just trafficking and pedophilia.
But this goes into you know black magic ritualistic behavior.
Oh let me tell you something. Eyes wide shut isn't a movie. It's a documentary.
You get in the upper echelons of money. You either got rich people that hide out and stay away from everybody or freaked out.
Or really rich people. Or you got rich people that are devil worshipping devil worshipping.
I mean I mean hardcore Luciferianism is is all over the place. I've told the story.
They're not making enough. I've seen it folks. OK. And that's when I was a teenager.
So let me tell you it is bad. I mean I've been in eyes wide shut stuff.
I've literally gotten out of that stuff 13 14 15.
I was like God I get to date the beauty queen. God I'm 15 dating a college beauty queen.
And I was like another big mansion another helicopter pad and more another black magic ceremony.
And I was just like God Almighty. They were trying to recruit me man. It's all over the place bro.
Oh I mean I know it. But how deep does it go and how prolific is it.
It's it's Luciferianism in elite rich circles.
That's the Bible says the devil controls the elite principalities the powers the air.
I mean I would say half the billionaires and their adjuncts in any elite area
are doing sex rituals and black magic on a weekly basis.
I mean it's it's there are as many satanic real churches not the fake idiot ones you see.
They're all idiots but you know the little provincials.
There are as many satanic ceremonies going on in a major city or in these elite rural areas
almost as much as there are church services going on.
Do you hear what I'm saying. Yeah of course.
Because this isn't like going down to the Baptist church in here in the preacher speaking
singing some hymns. There's sex whole nine yards.
What would this information coming out do to social order.
I just have the fear that Trump's trying to hide it because to just maintain the.
Yeah and I say let the chips fall where they may just to be done but they haven't fall
and from all my research in MO Trump would never put himself in the position
to go into a black mass and doing the things they do.
Most of it is a children but it's you know I mean it's something else.
I'll tell you that I was never in the rituals.
I got three or four times brought in and was like I'm getting out of here but I mean gorgeous women.
You know and boom I mean it's it's it's it's it's ritualistic sex.
It's it's what's what goes on and it's very seductive and you know it's where I grew up.
You could swing a stick in the dark and not hit it so I appreciate your call.
Good points. Andrew thank you so much.
You're on the air from Ohio. Go ahead.
Glad to be talking to you.
First time caller been listening about seven years or so to the program.
Want to do a quick bug for your your products.
My wife and I have been taking the methylene blue for a month or so now and what an amazing product.
I feel like a completely different person.
Energy levels are fantastic and and no let down so highly recommended.
You know and of course talk to your doctor first because it can have some interactions.
But wow what an amazing product.
So that's fantastic and we appreciate all the work that you're doing to expose some of what's going on in our society.
I was calling to talk about the Epstein debacle and kind of just touch on the point of why the popular opinion is so
insistent that we want some of this information to come out.
And I think that I probably speak for a lot of people in saying that we believe the Epstein situation is emblematic of a two tiered justice.
This employees one set of rules for certain people and another set of rules for the rest of it.
Exactly that's why people are so pissed and and it's all real.
There's been all these cases we know it.
We know there's a cover up and then Trump 180s.
Well yeah and I agree with your last caller in saying that some of the things we've seen Trump doing in the last couple weeks is totally out of character.
The flip flopping back and forth and somewhat unexplainable.
One of the things that I there are so many connections amongst the billionaires and the uber rich that aren't being talked about.
Well that's the thing is they're bored.
And so just like it came out in ancient medieval times there was all this devil worship going on.
It wasn't just the Inquisition was a bad to making it up.
I mean it was really these people get bored.
They're into it.
It's it leads to this throughout history.
Yeah that's the scary thing.
And of course I'm calling from Columbus Ohio and most people don't know that Jeffrey Epstein spent significant amounts of time here in Columbus.
And his connections with billionaire Les Wexner are extensive.
Oh he was definitely Wexner's Mossad for sure.
And he was Mossad CA as well.
They don't let you operate unless you're just a joint deal MI6 heavily through Maxwell.
And yeah 100% that's what this was.
He was just a front man.
He was just the major D.
He was just the butler.
The best thing now is that some of these connections amongst the uber wealthy and Jeffrey Epstein.
Just yesterday I saw a news article that more business dealings have come out as behind some of the A.I. movement.
The financiers behind them was Peter Teal, Jeffrey Epstein and Ahud Barak former Prime Minister of Israel.
And well absolutely everybody's investing in A.I. have been for decades.
Super interesting now is that there is a the Prometheus data center that Intel is building is being put up here in New Albany, Ohio.
Which is home of Leslie Wexner and L Brands and Delimited.
These are all Wexner's companies.
Absolutely we're out of time but absolutely it's intelligence operation.
All right we're going to start hour number three take a few more phone calls in the CIA whistleblower and more.
It's all coming up in hour number three.
Remember you're the Paul Revere's.
Share the live feeds from all the shows on X now, now, now, now.
You were just telling me that you had a brain disease and you what did you do to fix it?
I found this guy's a functional medicine guy and he got me on a methylene blue and that instantly stopped everything.
I take it.
Okay.
Yeah.
I take it every day as well.
RFK Junior told me about it.
Yeah man, it's fantastic.
And so this guy's injecting in 1890, injects these rats with it and then does an autopsy on these things and their brain, the brainstem, every single nerve is blue.
So he discovered this methylene blue has an affinity for neuronal tissue.
So he says well it's sucking into neurons and working in the body.
So he started putting it in humans.
And we found out it's an MAOL, which helps with depression and anxiety and all kinds of life stress and stuff.
It is so incredible that it acts as an electron donor to mitochondria, especially your neuronal mitochondria.
So it helps you produce more ATP and it helps you get rid of this stuff called reactive oxygen species.
So you have an oxygen molecule.
It should have two hydrogens on it and like your body's job is to convert stuff into water so you can pee it out.
So if you get an oxygen molecule it's got four, five, one, it's a reactive oxygen, which we call free radicals.
So methylene blue goes in there and balances a lot of those things out in your brain and your nervous system.
So it is a miracle and it's been proven for a hundred years.
It's one of the most well proven drugs out there.
The strongest medical grade methylene blue and this is what I'm on, total mitochondria cleaning, next level energy.
This is amazing.
You want to know what I'm on?
Iris Seymour Shilogy.
This right here.
Look at that.
That is power.
I'm on intermittent fasting.
I'm eight to three o'clock today and I stopped eating crap food.
Stop drinking.
That's what I'm on right there, baby.
If you are receiving this transmission, you are the resistance.
Call me for you.
I hate living here, sir.
I'm going to jump right into it.
Going off of what you said before you took the first caller, the mustad.
The mustad, I believe in the 70s and 80s, used a term called browning.
And that browning term was anybody in power in the Senate, judicial, you name it, you would just like the movie and the Godfather.
If they wake up, the senator would wake up and realize a child was in their bed.
So I definitely agree upon you on that.
And they're still in the same thing I believe to Trump.
And what immediately needs to be done, he didn't learn this his first term is everybody around him.
It's still a deep state.
And those same advisors, those same DC lawyers that have been in the swamp forever, and they're just keeping them busy.
They're just keeping them busy until his terms over.
And then they're going to get right back in and hit us with even more lockdowns and whatever they have planned for us to get us into that state.
So what he needs to do immediately is get rid of all those people, start listening to a general Flynn, these people that aren't in that swamp.
And you know what Owen actually touched on this on the show, I believe it was a couple of days ago and his Twitter.
Not only the people surrounding him, but he needs to start listening and posting stuff like that when he starts to researching those people around him.
What I mean is maybe having a show and touching look at this is his cabinet members by name.
They were, you know, doing this back in the 80s.
They were with the neocons.
And that's who those people are.
And that's who he's listening to.
He's getting still false information.
We found out that when they we had that missile attack and he ordered that.
That was all fake information.
But wait a minute.
Ben Shapiro said that the Israeli Prime Minister told him that Jonathan Pollard's the only Israeli spy in US history.
They don't spy on us and each her bunnies real too.
Oh, exactly.
That's the whole and the Mossad has been doing this and now they're infiltrating.
That is our our number one threat right now to the United States of America is being conquered within.
Well, Ben Shapiro said, don't listen to me.
He has almost no audience now.
People totally woken up to him and then he goes around dictating, telling people not to listen to me.
I mean, it just isn't an idiot.
And he literally is a mouthpiece of Netanyahu.
I believe it's we the people, not the one we the people that make those decisions.
Yeah, it's certainly again, I don't want the chai comms running us.
I don't want the British running us and I don't want Israel running us.
It's just Israel wouldn't put up with that crap from us.
So quit treating us like a doormat.
And then this special council, I believe we've been down this road before with a special council.
How many years is that going to take?
Is the statute of limitations going to be up by then?
Well, it's already up.
But there's not a conspiracy in that.
And that's the new FBI grand conspiracy probe.
We'll see they fired Cummy's daughter today.
So I mean, I hear you.
I'll say this.
I'm not telling her about a cover up.
I don't want him to.
But for God's sakes, if he's going to try to move on from this for whatever reasons,
maybe on the economy or whatever, not endorsing it, but I could get the reasoning,
at least understand why that has some logic.
Then stop saying don't look at it and stop saying there's nothing there.
That makes it 10 times worse.
A special council.
I think I'm Ed Martin, I would trust.
And then and I think we can, you know, really get to the bottom of it and use it
against the Democrats because they're the ones in to it up their eyeballs.
Thank you, Jeff.
We got the CIA whistleblower.
They'll continue on with your phone calls after he leaves us.
Stay there.
We'll be right back.
Alex wanted you.
He gave you the methylene blue drink earlier.
Is that correct?
Yeah.
And he wanted you to do a review.
Hey, I can feel a definite like an energy spike.
Yeah, it feels pretty good.
What are you going to do now?
No energy spike.
I'm going to see if it has a crash.
I've never heard of a crash.
Yeah, probably it doesn't.
But yeah, it feels pretty good.
Yeah, definitely a full sharper.
Okay.
Yeah, that's pretty tired.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, you're running around Texas right now.
You're dealing with some other issues here.
I was driving all over Texas,
by Jake and that was pretty, pretty efficient.
Nice.
Yeah, it feels pretty good.
So did he give you the drink or the capsules?
I took the drink, but I got a bottle of each
and I'm going to go and do a longer term test.
We'll see how it goes.
Okay.
Yeah, I do feel kind of amped right now.
Yeah.
That's good.
Well, that's probably, I don't know,
that might be because you're hanging out with me.
So we got to maybe try to get a review of it.
I think it's about the lean blue.
Teamstream media, government cover-ups.
You want to stop tyranny?
Well, so does he.
Live from the info wars.com studios.
It's Alex Jones.
I've been John Kiriakou for over a decade longer
since the deep state because he quietly, privately
tried to get them to stop illegally torturing people
when he was the head of counterterrorism in Afghanistan
and then other areas.
So I'm going to wear him since that happened
however many decades ago it was
and getting targeted by the bushes and all the rest of them.
And I've read a lot of his writings
and I have just from the other day,
I actually have one of his books.
I read it years ago.
He's the best-selling author as well.
And we've done a couple good interviews with him.
But man, I saw him on Tucker.
I saw him on some other interviews.
And I was like, wow, I want to get that guy on
because I was kind of guiding it with, you know,
the questions I had at the time about Iran
and where that was going.
But he has had experiences.
And again, I'm not on a jag here to attack Israel
and just obsess on that all day.
And I don't believe that again,
Israel previously was a dominant force
other than our foreign policy in the Middle East,
which General Wesley Clark and others exposed.
We already knew it.
Project New Record Century, you know,
Israeli neocons, U.S. neocons,
Rumsfeld, Wormser, all of them
won to take down in just five years, seven countries.
Well, here we are 25 years later
and they're 24 years later
and they've gotten six and now they won Iran,
who's allied with China and Russia and is, you know, not Iraq.
And it's now never been clear though
that Israel, because of the power vacuum
and the Democrats in trouble
and the lowest fundraising ever
and their poll numbers the lowest ever,
I mean, they're badly coordinated.
Trump's cutting off the NGO money.
They're redistricting.
They're going after the election fraud.
They're cutting off funding to the states.
You know, they don't put in voter ID.
I mean, we're on a roll that this is great
except into that vacuum.
We dealt with eight, nine years ago,
the Democrats, Deep State, Brennan Clapper, Comey.
I was targeted.
That's now been declassified partially
along with Trump in SA wiretaps, all of it,
starting in 2013,
because I knew Trump was getting ready to run.
And I was lumped into that.
And so I wouldn't call Brennan Clapper, Obama,
you know, Israel operatives.
I mean, they worked with Israel,
but they were funding Arab Spring
in their own, you know, agendas.
But now, in my view,
well researched, it is accurate to say
China was the main threat.
Obviously nobody debated that
of espionage and economic and military threats.
And then you can move down the chain from that.
Obviously Russia in there.
But no, Israel, not as a military threat, per se,
other than dragging us into war.
So I guess it is.
This is the top threat kind of other than NATO
keeping this thing going for Russia.
But so I would say that the second largest military threat
by proxy or by black hole.
And then they are, in my view, the number one espionage
beyond espionage, really soft coup threat
with them moving into the vacuum of the White House.
And then there's the taboo of criticizing, you know,
anything Israel you could call baby Hitler.
No, Israel is a powerful, sophisticated group.
And it's a fact, in my view,
that they are now attempting a coup
over the policies of the United States
and not just militarily,
but what companies get chosen for AI funding, all of it.
And with their history of transfers to China and others,
it's just insane.
So I heard John Kiryaki on several shows
and he experienced that.
I only read one of his books.
He's got, I think, 10 or more.
The point is he witnessed what I've been told
by a lot of, I've had Mossad whistleblowers,
famous ones on the show talking about this decades ago.
But the fact that he never ran into any intelligence agency
that behaved or acted like this.
And so I kind of been ranting there.
I don't know his exact assessment of this,
but does he think, in general, when I said it's accurate
or can he give us who he thinks the main threats are
and then looking into this, what he thinks of my statement
that, I mean, I don't think it's even debatable
that this is an attempted Israeli Likudnik takeover.
And they kind of had that with George W. Bush,
at least on foreign policy.
And then how he thinks we could extricate ourselves from that
or does he disagree with that?
And what does he think of the bizarre Streisand effect?
I mean, Trump couldn't be doing something worse
to tie himself to Epstein as saying move on.
There's nothing to see here.
These aren't the droids you're looking for.
You've got all that.
So John Kiryakou, find all his books
and substack everything at JohnKiryakou.substack.com,
JohnKiryakou.com, K-I-R-I-A-K-O-U.
And so much more.
He's a journalist and former C.I. counterterrorism officer.
He had a counterterrorism post like Afghanistan.
And I won't go over his whole bio.
And he was an internal whistleblower.
So they tried to set him up.
That's all been proven.
So thank you so much, John, for joining us.
That was a long intro.
You've got the floor.
Thank you so much.
I have to say that I do agree with you.
I've said for a very long time,
and I'm going to stake out really the same position
that you just staked out.
This has nothing to do with whether or not we like Israel.
This has nothing to do with whether or not
we believe Israel has a right to exist.
Of course it has a right to exist.
Nobody's debating that.
At least very few people are debating that.
But the issue is we cannot chain ourselves to Israel
for better or for worse
and just pretend that Israel's interests
are always our interests.
It's just simply not the case.
And I have to say I laughed out loud
when I saw on the clip that you ran
the Israelis claiming that they haven't spied on us
since Jonathan Pollard.
That is just simply false.
I was in a debate with the former head of Mossad
and Alan Dershowitz a few weeks ago
on the Pierce Morgan show.
And the former head of Mossad, General Danny, something,
said exactly the same thing.
Well, we haven't spied on the United States
since Jonathan Pollard.
That's just not true.
Pollard was arrested in 1985.
The year of the spy, if you remember,
that's what Ronald Reagan declared it.
The year of the spy.
In 1990, five years later,
on my very first day at the CIA,
the CIA's head of security told us
that the FBI had identified 187
undeclared Israeli intelligence officers
spread all around the country
for the purpose of stealing our defense secrets.
They're targeting almost exclusively
American defense contractors.
And yes, they are a threat to our national security.
And it's on record they sell it to China.
That's not very friendly.
That's the whole problem there.
You know, on the one hand, we would say,
okay, it might even be akin to Canada
stealing our secrets.
All right, they shouldn't, but what are you going to do?
But it's not just that they steal our secrets
to ensure that they are as safe as possible.
They steal our secrets to then sell
to the Russians or the Chinese
or not even to sell so much as to trade.
For example, Jonathan Pollard,
whose picture is on the screen right now,
one of the most prolific spies in American history
has been in prison for 30 years
and did every single day of the 30 years.
Jonathan Pollard gave the Israelis
information on Russian,
I'm sorry, Soviet troop movements, for example.
The Israeli government then gave
that top secret information to the Soviets
in exchange for the release of Soviet Jews
and permission for them to emigrate to Israel.
Well, you know what?
I feel bad for the Soviet Jews
and what they went through in the 1980s,
but it is not up to the likes of Jonathan Pollard
or the Israeli government to decide
that the Soviet Union should have
top secret American defense information.
Well, Pollard wasn't a U.S. citizen
or remember correctly, but it's treason.
Oh yeah, he was.
He was and he was working for the defense
or the Naval Intelligence Service.
Yeah, I was kind of back at the question.
The point is that's treason.
Exactly. Yes.
So, but it's like, oh, it's okay.
He did it for Israel.
So he can give the Soviets our main enemy
with nuclear submarines pointing missiles at us.
That's okay.
It's just, it's preposterous.
It is. It's outrageous.
You know, I spoke with a contact
at the Israeli embassy recently
and he said something that really bothered me very much.
He said that embassy officials here in Washington
are under orders to equate anti-Zionism
with anti-Semitism.
They've had success in doing this so far,
but they want to, they want to get us to a point
where if you disagree publicly
with anything that the Israeli government does,
it's because you're anti-Semitic.
Well, a bunch of states, sir, as you know,
Texas is the worst and I overall like the governor,
but on this he's crazy.
He's sanctioning San Marcus,
the big city south of Maine from Austin
because some of their city council had a vote
against the indiscriminate killing of civilians in Gaza
and he's saying, well, you know,
we're going to sanction you and put controls
and now they're making any business
that gets a state contract pledge allegiance to Israel.
Have you seen this?
That's right.
I have seen it.
A friend of mine was contracted to give a speech
at Georgia State University
and she was told that she had to sign
a loyalty pledge to Israel as well.
She said, I'm American.
I'm not Israeli.
I'm not going to sign a loyalty pledge.
And so they canceled her speech.
Now she's filed a civil question.
I want to add, and I'm not saying it's one monolithic group,
but Netanyahu and their lobby.
I mean, it's like, it's like Nick Fuentes,
he worked to the daily wire was pro-Israel.
So they tried to make him go to Israel,
tried to sheep dip him basically in their operations.
He said, why are you doing this?
I thought you're American.
So then they fired him
and then tried to get him banned everywhere.
And then he turned into this.
Don't they understand like going out
and saying you got to sign loyalty pledges
and like 15 states to have a state contract
or these big people go, well, why do I have to do that?
I mean, I couldn't figure out a way
to turn people against me more.
Oh my gosh, exactly right.
Exactly right.
Even for people who don't follow these issues
and don't care one way or the other about Israel.
If somebody plopped a declaration in front of you
and said, you have to sign this
you cannot have the contract.
And what they're asking you to sign
is a declaration saying that you will never criticize Israel.
Who in their right mind would sign something like this?
That's not a weird social credit score.
Well, remember McCarthy and others
in Eisenhower for a little while with Nixon
wanted loyalty oaths in the government
that you were loyal to the U.S. and not a communist
and people said that's unconstitutional.
And I could see it was a little too far
saying you're loyal to the U.S. is bad,
but you can say you got to be loyal to Israel
when you're in a U.S. citizen.
Yeah, it doesn't make any kind of sense at all.
I shouldn't laugh because it's not funny.
It's actually quite dangerous.
And I'll tell you, one of the things that bothers me
the very, very most is that
the Christian community here in the United States
should be up in arms over things like this.
The Israelis have essentially wiped out
the indigenous Christian community in Israel
in the West Bank and in Gaza.
Two weeks ago, they just burned down
one of the oldest Christian settlements
the Jewish settlers did.
That's exactly right. They burned it down
and they destroyed St. Porfirio's church in Gaza.
The oldest continually operating Christian church
anywhere in the world.
And what we're not permitted to complain about that,
it doesn't make sense.
So where do you see this going
and looking at the Trump administration
that you're dialed in?
How much Israeli infiltration?
We can't say exactly, but it's pretty blatant at this point.
I mean, we know they're in control
of the Middle Eastern policy to a great extent,
but I mean, it looks like they're going for broke.
How bad is it?
I think it's bad.
But I will say that the move
of the American embassy in Israel
from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem aside,
I think that President Trump is very serious
when he talks about guaranteeing Israel's right to exist
and guaranteeing Israel's security. That's fine.
I think he truly believes
that the Abraham Accords are a force for peace
and that things will get better
if Saudi Arabia joins the Abraham Accords.
Great.
But President Trump is in this unique situation right now
where he can be the one
to bring some sort of real peace to the region.
There was a piece in Haaretz,
the wonderful Israeli newspaper just a couple of weeks ago,
saying that one of the things that the president is suggesting
and we haven't seen this from the American side yet.
We've seen it only in Haaretz,
but one of the things that the president is suggesting
is that Gaza fall administratively
under the auspices of Saudi Arabia
that it disarm, so there would be no Gaza military
or Gaza police force.
The Saudis would develop the Gaza economy
by building a port and airport.
Flood it with money.
Flood it with money. Put everybody to work.
Allow them to manufacture something that they can export.
And then you don't need all this fighting anymore.
And then Netanyahu steps up a tax because he doesn't want that.
Exactly.
Just like Israel helped create Hamas to destabilize it.
It's the same story.
Yes, couldn't agree more.
That is disgusting.
It's awful and what's incredible to me is that he doesn't see
how incredibly short-sighted this is.
I was in a restaurant in New York the other day
and I was talking to a friend of mine having lunch with a friend of mine
and we were talking about these very issues
and there were these two women next to us,
both in their 80s and they were quietly listening to what we had to say
and then finally one of them said,
excuse me, I couldn't help but to overhear your conversation.
We're both Jewish and we agree with you on this issue.
They said Netanyahu is so far to the right
that he's forcing people who otherwise would be pro-Israel
or wouldn't be paying attention one way or the other
to become anti-Israel and it's a short walk
from being anti-Israel to being anti-Semitic
that it is Netanyahu who is creating anti-Semitism.
I totally agree.
Michael Savage is a pro-American.
He's not an Israel first guy but he's pro-Israel.
He says Netanyahu needs to go.
Just a couple of days ago I was on the Pierce Morgan show again
and I was on with Jack Busoviec and two left-wing bloggers
and at the end Pierce asked us about our position on Israel.
Every one of the four of us said,
of course Israel has a right to exist.
Israel has a right to defend itself but my God,
slaughtering tens of thousands, hundreds of thousands perhaps
of women, children, elderly.
You flatten all seven of them.
On TV, on TV.
It's the first televised genocide
and then you flatten all of the hospitals.
There's not enough food for anybody.
People are dying of thirst.
Come on, where's the end here?
There's too much.
And then Pierce said that that was probably the first time
that he added four guests who agreed across the board on Israel.
Well, and then you've got the left that is just frothing
basically pro-Hitler now while they call conservatives Hitler
with no evidence.
Yeah, that doesn't help.
It doesn't help.
No.
No, that doesn't help.
We've got to be constructive.
Like you just said, this is a genocide.
And there is still a chance to save some people.
So we've got to do the right thing here.
We've got to stand up to the Israelis.
What happened on October 7th, he announced, you know,
out of the Old Testament, the ethnic cleansing.
I mean, he said, we're going to cleanse this.
And if you look at the international accords that
have been signed since the end of the Second World War,
this is the definition.
This is the legal definition of ethnic cleansing
and ethnic cleansing is a form of genocide.
And remember, a year ago, Netanyahu floated a memo
to move the Gazans, not to Egypt, but to Europe and the U.S.
It's just, and again, people don't know, Saudi Arabia
is reforming a lot of you and they're more of an expert than I.
They are really working with Israel.
They've talked to Trump.
They would set it all up, have security,
turn it into a beautiful golf courses, hotels, beautiful beach.
Everybody would have jobs.
They would kick Hezbollah, Hamas out.
And it would be great.
They would have a trading partner right there.
And Saudi Arabia is like ready.
And they're reforming and they're saying women
are going to get the burkas off.
I mean, so we see reform starting.
And Netanyahu is like, no, we're taking it all.
And they think we can't do translation.
We can watch the national TV shows in Hebrew.
And I mean, it is just frothing, absolutely frothing.
We're going to kill all these people.
And they don't know that people are watching that.
Yeah, seriously.
You know, on my very first overseas tour with the CIA,
I was stationed in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia.
And toward the end of my tour, the Saudis came to us.
They came to talk to the US ambassador,
Ambassador Chas Freeman.
And they said, look, we have this idea for Gaza.
Hamas had just been formed,
but they had this idea for Gaza,
where they go in and they work with the Israelis
to build a port and an airport.
And that would allow the Israelis to
ship things out of Gaza, would put Gazans to work.
Maybe they could encourage some manufacturing.
They would allow fishing.
For example, the Gazans are not allowed to fish.
Can you imagine?
It's a coastal enclave and they're not allowed to fish.
And so we went to the Israelis informally and said,
look, the Saudis are willing to pay for all this.
They want to bring electricity.
They want to bring clean water and a port and an airport.
And the Israelis said, absolutely not.
Now that was 34 years ago.
And we're still having the same conversation.
Yeah.
And then again, for people out there,
Netanyahu says he's defending civilization.
You don't create Hamas, have them destabilize it admittedly
so there's not a good leadership that's reasonable.
Lately, Turkey, NATO and Israel put in
the leader of al-Qaeda in Syria.
And Israel goes, well, we blew up their military, so it's OK.
It's total statelet destabilization, great game,
balkanization crap, and it's evil.
And the public understands it.
Not the crazy left kill all the two people.
We're not talking about the Soros, funny people,
who I think they fund to do that to actually bolster it.
But we're talking about reasonable people like Trump
wanting to fix this and Netanyahu saying no,
and then waving his moral flag around, you know,
that he's against Hamas when he's been their sugar daddy
I'm glad you used the word balkanization just now
because that's exactly what we're seeing happen.
And we're seeing it happen in slow motion.
You mentioned at the start of this segment that
there's one of the last Christian villages
in the West Bank is being wiped out this week.
As we speak, there are Israeli settlers
from New Jersey and New York
and they're forcing Palestinian Christians out of their homes
burning down their olive trees
and they're just taking their land, seizing their land.
Well, what we're seeing if you look at a map of the West Bank,
now is you see these little circles and they dot the map
and those are Israeli settlements.
That's what Bosnia looks like, right?
That's what Republika Srpska looks like in the Balkans.
It's these little islands surrounded by the land
of another state
and these little statelets don't work.
They don't work.
Well, like I said, Trump coming out and saying
don't look into Absteen is a total strident effect
of five-year-old would know that.
Israel on TV saying we're taking all the land
from the Christians, from the Muslims, it's ours
and we're going to kill everybody
and announcing the biblical names for that.
This is like this week and then saying,
well, we're not doing anything wrong when the whole world sees it.
Do you think Israel and the Likudiks are in a bubble?
I mean, do they not know what they're doing?
I think that they are so confident
in continued support from the United States
that they can do anything that they want.
They don't really care what, let's say,
the French have to say or the Chinese have to say.
They care only what the Americans have to say
because they need our veto in the United Nations Security Council.
And so long as the Americans don't put pressure on them,
they'll just continue to push the envelope
to see how far they can go.
Well, I mean, just the last few years,
you'd think October 7th Israel popularity goes up,
then they don't just kill the leaders of the groups,
they go after the civilians, and now the polls show
Israel is basically the most unpopular country in the world.
Yeah, and that's not happened before.
You know, every single year, Gallup International
does a global poll where they ask people in every country on Earth
who the greatest threat to world peace is.
And you know, for the Greeks it's the Turks,
and the Turks it's the Greeks,
Pakistanis and the Indians the same thing,
the North Koreans and the South Koreans the same thing.
You expect that.
For the rest of the world,
it's usually the United States is the greatest threat.
Stay there. We gotta go to break.
Let's come back with that right now.
And it's got a special system where the knife doesn't come out
when it's upside down.
It takes a little pull to get it out.
It is amazing.
This is, in my opinion, the very best defense battle dagger
you can get.
It's an incredible price for $79.99 right now.
This knife by itself, it stores sales for $100
every day that we bought.
5,000 of them, so got the price down really low.
All sales, we can pass that on to you,
and the profit we make goes in to fund this operation.
It's got a great defensive system for yourself and your family,
great in your car, great on your side, great in your purse,
your glove compartment, also skin a buck with it,
whatever you need.
This is an amazing knife.
You not only, though, get something to defend yourself,
you defend the Republic in the information war
by funding this operation.
So get your limited edition Alex Jones signature battle dagger
at thealexjonesstore.com right now,
and it keeps this operation on the air.
This isn't just a blade.
It's a symbol of freedom.
Limited edition Alex Jones signature battle dagger
is forged by patriots ready to defend the Republic
from the globalist agenda featuring a double-edged
black coated blade for unmatched durability
and precision this dagger is built to last.
On one side is my signature,
while the other side proudly bears 1776,
a reminder that the spirit of revolution
lives on stronger than ever.
With its ergonomic non-slip grip designed ready
for any mission the dagger isn't just a tool,
it's a statement.
Whether you're adding it to your collection
or keeping it close as a symbol of resistance
or for defense, this blade is for those who know
that the answer in 1984 is 1776 kickers now.
And then we're announcing a limited sale,
the power drive bundle of power plant and methyl drive,
which goes incredibly good with methylene blue.
And both of these give you incredible natural energy
clarity and focus, but you mix them together
with methylene blue, I will tell you
in Chase Geyser's observation himself,
10 times stronger than turbo force.
Did you hear what I just said?
Get yours now.
Discounted massively.
50% off when you get them together.
50% off on the power drive bundle for a limited time
one week at thealexjonesstore.com
and it funds this operation 7076 worldwide.
Feeding a frontal assault on the lies of the New World Order.
It's Alex Jones from the info wars.com studios.
It's Alex Jones.
You keep saying you've been a messin'
where you shouldn't have been a messin'.
And now some are your best.
These boots are made, boots are gonna walk all over.
You know, we got words for it in different languages.
You got bravada, you got arrogance, you got hubris,
you got hutzpah.
What Israel is doing and continues to do
is very self-destructive.
And so our guest, John Kiriakou,
very famous CIA whistleblower,
former counterterrorism officer,
head of counterterrorism in Afghanistan and other countries,
I want to soon move into Epstein and other issues
and, you know, what else is on your radar,
but just finishing up, you got caught off by the break.
The polls everywhere, you're mentioning, I think, a Gallup poll.
We covered that a while back.
For the first time ever,
Israel is seen around the world as the number one threat to world peace.
But you were going to actually over the numbers.
I don't have the poll in front of me, but it seems you do.
So just finish up, John, sorry, that break was a hard break.
Oh, no, that's okay.
Yeah, now the Israelis are seen as the greatest threat to world peace.
And here we are all these years later,
all these rounds of negotiations later,
all these different ideas later,
and not only has nothing changed,
the situation has become even worse.
So I know it's hard to predict things,
but in the short term, midterm, long term,
it looks to me like the Israeli control of the White House
is getting more intense.
And I'm seeing major pressure, though, everywhere
and a real awakening to this that was already happening,
but now it's supercharged.
And it's not how the Israel lobby wants to brand it as pro-Hitler
or pro-radical Islam.
That's not working.
And then I understand Israel's nuclear weapons are not going anywhere.
I don't want them destroyed.
I think they have a right to exist.
I mean, I literally am not sitting here obsessed with Jews all day.
But with these policies and the Hutzpah issue,
Israel is now seen as the main villain.
And they can't just juxtapose it to the unpopular mullahs either.
People are more sophisticated.
On this trajectory, where do you see this going?
I honestly don't see it getting any better.
And part of the reason is that this is not at all a partisan issue.
Democrats and Republicans' ideas about Israel
are almost identical, at least within the mainstream.
Of course, there are going to be these radicals
on the far left and on the far right
that are going to have a different position.
But there's no pressure from the United States
for the Israelis to change their position.
And there are no bold desires or propositions
for overarching peace agreements.
We're not seeing calls for Oslo, another Oslo round.
We're not seeing calls for a grand deal
to make all of these issues go away.
And in fact, I think that the Saudis
would be interested in participating in something like that.
Undoubtedly, the Qataris would be interested in participating.
The Palestinians would probably beg to participate in something.
But the Israelis know that nobody's going to force them.
And so there's no incentive for them to go to the negotiating table.
So what happens in Gaza?
And then, of course, they're just going to expand more in the Golan.
They're going to expand to the West Bank.
There is a greater Israel project.
That's not a conspiracy theory.
They wear it on their army IDF uniforms.
Hell, they want, like, to make Israel 10 times bigger.
That's insane.
Yeah.
In fact, they bombed Syria again today.
And the Syrians, you know, the Syrian government
is just this little radical statelet
that's trying to convince everybody
that they've left their radicalism behind them.
And I hope to God that they have.
But the Israelis are free just to come and go
and bomb anybody they want.
And they do it.
They do it all the time.
So what do I expect in Gaza?
I expect more of the same.
I think that the plan is to turn the whole place to rubble.
And it's to force Gazans out.
You mentioned a few minutes ago
that the Israelis had been encouraging Palestinians
to move to the United States or move to Egypt
or move to Jordan.
And when that wasn't forthcoming,
they came up with this cockamamie plan
to take all the Gaza Palestinians
and send them to Albania.
And the Albanians said, well, we don't want them.
We want our own economic problems.
Then they came up with this stupid idea
to send them all to an island off the coast of Indonesia.
And the Indonesians said, well, we don't know anything about this.
We know we're not giving up an island to become Palestine.
The truth is, all of those are forms of genocide.
Forced removal of a temple is a form of genocide.
And we have the multi-thousand-year-old,
three-thousand-year-old Moses and the Jews
being kicked out of Egypt
and then the Jews and the dysporos and Hitler.
And they're literally doing what was done to them now.
Exactly.
It wasn't right then.
And it's not right now.
Wow.
And then you go, oh, there's all sorts of things
that are Palestinian.
None of them live there.
I mean, it's just...
Oh, I hate that argument so much.
Don't you love Ben Shapiro?
You mentioned it earlier, but you didn't say his name.
He and others are like, there was only one Israeli spy,
Jonathan Pollard.
The former prime minister told me we don't spy on the US.
But when Ted Cruz got asked about it a few weeks ago
by Tucker, he said, well, of course they spy on us.
They're our friends.
Of course they do.
Yeah.
They always have.
It's as simple as that.
And if you talk to anybody who has served
at the American embassy in Israel,
whether when it was going to be for now...
I saw you on a podcast.
I forget which one.
Tell that story.
Describe out of all the intelligence agencies
you've dealt with, I imagine it's dozens.
Tell us how many, you know, directly...
You've been all the world.
Who is the most aggressive and the most deceptive?
Yeah.
By far the Mossad.
There's just, hands down, there's just no comparison.
I told the story on a podcast where two friends of mine
with whom I worked at the CIA were transferred to Israel
and they were both known to the Israeli services.
They were declared.
What's called declared to the Israeli services.
So when they arrive in Israel,
the station chief takes them to the Mossad
and says, you know my two people here.
They're going to be here for two years.
They're not going to be working against Israel, of course.
The wife is going to work on Palestinian issues
at the embassy and the husband is going to take Arabic classes
at the university.
Everybody's happy.
But then the ambassador has a welcome party for them
and when they get back home from the welcome party,
somebody had rearranged all the furniture
in their living room just as a signal that,
hey, we can mess with you anytime we want.
And of course they reported it.
Several months later, the ambassador has a Christmas party.
They go to the Christmas party and they come back
and people had defecated in all of the toilets in their house
and left it unflushed.
Now, why would you do that?
Just to intimidate, just to anger
and just to show disrespect.
Finally, another year and a half passes.
It's time for them to leave.
The ambassador has a going away party for them.
They go to the party.
They drive back to Jerusalem.
People had gone into the house.
The dog was whimpering under the dining room table.
They had cut the dog's tail off
and they wrapped it in gauze and in medical tape.
Now, why would you do something like that?
What do you hope to accomplish just by treating an ally that way?
And of course, the CIA has to go to the Israelis
and say, stop harassing our people.
And the Israelis say, okay, okay.
And then they're good for a year or two.
And then they just start doing it again.
But that's the nature of our relationship.
That is not how you make friends and influence people.
No.
I mean, take Sibachanik.
I know he worked in Intelligence Bunch of Places,
co-authored books with Tom Clancy.
But he's Jewish, by the way.
He said no.
He said there's nothing worse than when he dealt with
over the decades with Israel and all the rest of it.
Also, I tell another story about them coming to the embassy
and meeting with you guys and always giving gifts
with open bugs in them knowing you're going to find it.
Like, is it just like they don't want you there?
I mean, but this is our loving ally, our best little pal.
Yeah, this is something else that we had to deal with.
You carry on liaison meetings all the time
with visiting intelligence services,
literally every single day.
And the Israelis, we had to stop allowing
onto the CIA headquarters campus
because every time they'd come, they would bring a gift.
And every time they brought a gift,
it had a listening device installed inside
and it was packed with batteries.
And we would tell them, you guys have to stop doing this.
Every time you come here, you try to bug our conference rooms.
So now when we meet with the Israelis, it's off campus.
You just can't trust them.
And by the way, if I as a U.S. citizen, let's say,
asked for a tour and I got caught it lately
even in the cafeteria, placing a bug.
I'd probably get 20 years of prison.
Test me an option.
Without any question, you would go straight to federal prison.
Yes.
So, and if I work for the CIA and I leak something,
I'd go to jail.
So the point is, is that how,
I don't even understand the psychology of that.
And not just you telling me this has come out.
Why, what is the motive of behaving like this?
I've been told that the motive is the desire,
the unequivocal desire for survival,
that the Israelis understand, sure, we're friends, we're allies,
but nobody can save the Israelis, but the Israelis at the end of the day.
And on the off chance that we're not giving them
literally everything we have in terms of defense and intelligence,
then by God, they're going to steal it from us
and they're going to use it to protect themselves.
Don't they get being highly aggressive like that?
Is what's turning everybody against them?
I don't think they care.
Well, let me ask you this.
I think they don't care.
Did you ever see grading them, were there other agencies,
because everybody really studies history,
I'm not an intelligence expert, I've studied, it's very interesting.
You know, the Russians are all just straight up,
we love you, we're your friend, you want sex, you want money.
The Chinese, same deal.
You know, sex operative, stuff like that.
But instead the Israelis is just pure muscle,
pure in your face, pure blackmail, pure attack.
That historically, I would think would be the,
I know I've read books about interrogators and how to monitor people.
Like usually it's the good cop that gets people to do what they want.
Exactly.
So why do they behave like this?
Alex, with, I never encountered another intelligence service
that didn't understand from deep down,
didn't understand that it is the light touch
that wins a person over.
It's the good cop who wins the person over.
You can't just punch people in the face over and over and over
and over and over and expect them to do your bidding
or to treat you like an equal and a friend.
The Russians would never treat people like this,
the Chinese, the Cubans, the British.
I mean how do they operate?
I already said the British were about the best you'd seen,
but I mean describe the British versus the Russians,
it's so interesting, or the Chinese.
You engage a person in conversation
and that conversation you want to eventually lead to friendship
and when the conversation leads to friendship,
the friendship is going to lead to something even closer
to the point where this person is going to be willing
to commit espionage for you,
or in some cases to commit treason for you
just because you are their best friend.
When I first got hired at the CIA,
I asked a question in training
about the use of honey pots, for example.
A honey pot is when you try to entrap someone using sex
and my instructor said, oh no, no,
we haven't done that since the 50s.
That just doesn't work.
It makes people angry.
It doesn't allow you to create a relationship
based on trust, right?
And you want the relationship really to be based on trust.
Well, the Israelis don't care if you like them
or trust them.
They're going to punch you in the face
and they're going to poop in your toilets
and they're going to cut your dog's tail off
and then they're going to run a guy against you
in Congress because you're not pro-Israeli enough.
I never understood it.
And so I go back to the Nick Fuentes thing,
very popular, very articulate.
I don't agree with many things he says,
but I didn't know his origin story
until the day I did an interview
and I actually watched part of it
and it was true.
He was pro-Israel working at the daily wire
and they literally tried to get him to go to Israel,
make him do all this pro-Israel stuff.
He goes, what's this about Israel?
So he starts investigating and finds out
basically they're at Israeli front,
probably actually a Mossad.
We know these billionaires out of Texas
that are Zionists funded.
And then they fire him and persecute him
and come after him and then turn him
into this big enemy.
It's just crazy.
It is crazy.
It is crazy because you know
the number of people who are willing to put up with this
has to be finite.
At some point people have to stand up and say
enough is enough, America first.
We're not doing this anymore
and we are not going to let you treat us this way.
I mean, I'm not the toughest guy around.
I never started five people for no reason,
but I've certainly learned
even just a regular little skinny guy
washed his car.
You go over and knock on the side of the head.
He's probably going to attack you.
I mean, I just don't,
and then Israel's like, oh, we're loving.
Oh, we're friendly.
Oh, we're all this other stuff.
And then everybody I talked to including Jews
that have been in the CIA say, no, Israel's the worst.
And it didn't just start yesterday.
I mean, it's just bizarre.
Yeah, it's not good at all.
I don't know how they get anything accomplished internationally.
When you pick fights with everybody,
including or especially with your closest friends
in the world, it just doesn't make any sense.
So is there any,
are there any good factions in Israel
or how could Israel reform itself?
Because I really want Israel to succeed
and not be the detonator for nuclear war.
Well, there's been this odd political change in Israel
and it's being attributed to the influx
just over the last 20 or 30 years
of thousands and thousands of Jews
from the former Soviet Union,
but especially Russia and Ukraine.
They've pushed the body politic so far to the right
that Likud, if you can imagine this,
Likud is now seen as one of the moderate factions.
The only way to really change this
is to change the political system.
And I'm going to tell you what the Greeks did
because this actually has worked.
Greece had the same kind of system that Israel did
where there were 35 different political parties.
Nobody ever got a majority.
And so you had one weak coalition government after the next
like Israel has now.
In fact, the government technically collapsed yesterday
in Israel and Netanyahu now leads a minority government.
There hasn't been a call for a vote of no confidence,
but it's probably coming.
So what the Greeks did is they changed the electoral law
saying that you had to have 5% of the vote
to get elected to parliament.
So there are still minor parties that are represented there.
But whoever came in first got an extra 50 seats in parliament
and that way one single party has the authority to govern.
That's the only way they're going to be able
to get past this in Israel.
Otherwise, they're going to be at the beck and call
of these crazy religious parties where the leaders of these parties...
Any time a cult is under attack, it tends to get more extreme,
more in the bubble.
And again, Israel's leadership is its own worst enemy.
I'm serious, folks.
I literally care about Israel.
I mean, it's got nuclear weapons,
so I care about it not getting cornered.
So in closing, I can talk to you for hours.
Everybody should get your books.
Amazing, sir.
You're very busy.
Epstein.
And I'm not trying to go back to Israel again,
but obviously intelligence agency.
Maxwell, MI6, Russia, Assad,
buried Mount Olives military burial.
You've got, even though he was in Eastern Europe
World War II, I mean, all of that.
And then Trump's bizarre behavior in the last 12 days,
flip-flopping, creating mass drives and effects.
What is your view?
What are your sources?
What in the hell is going on here?
And is Israel using the Epstein file
that we know the Democrats and Brett and them had
and probably took out something about them
and stuck something about Trump
and told that's what it is?
You know, it's fake.
And now Trump is just sick of it,
but he's created this drives-in effect.
That's a huge subject.
But what do you think is going on?
Yeah, I think this has been handled very poorly.
I really believe that Donald Trump
doesn't have anything to hide.
He's been very transparent about his one-time friendship
with Jeffrey Epstein.
And I also believe that the FBI
probably has destroyed evidence,
maybe not in the last couple of weeks.
Maybe it happened four years ago
or 10 years ago, or who knows?
But, you know, when we talk about files,
we're not necessarily talking about paper files
in an envelope that says, you know,
evidence of pedophilia.
We're talking about computer hard drives
and disks and videos and DVDs.
There has to be something out there.
And I think that the American people
and the victims of Jeffrey Epstein
deserve an answer.
You're showing the Maxwell family,
including Ghislaine,
and Ghislaine Maxwell's father was a well-known Israeli
asset, Mossad asset.
I've said this before.
I'll say it again.
I think I feel very strongly about this.
I think that Jeffrey Epstein was a Mossad access agent.
I think that the support of Jeffrey Epstein
as someone who was just a proud and loyal Jew
and not an access agent that we're hearing
from the likes of Alan Dershowitz is nonsense.
And I think the only way to put this thing to bed
is the president is going to have to have
literally everything released.
When Pam Bondi said last week
that the videos that they have
showed child pornography and pedophilia,
they're disgusting, they're never going to be released,
but that's great.
That's fine.
We don't want to see videos of child pornography.
They said we want child porn.
No, we want the perpetrators prosecuted.
Exactly.
We want child porn released.
Identify the men on those tapes
and prosecute them.
That's all we're asking.
So let me ask you this.
There was an analyst
and former counterterrorism head.
Trump's body language,
I mean, it was angry, scared at the press conferences,
flipping out saying they manipulated the file,
which the total Democrat angle Brennan did have.
So that makes sense.
But just the handling of it and the behavior.
I keep saying this.
You couldn't behave worse to act incriminated.
And then people thought I was attacking Trump.
I was saying, I'm scared.
I mean, this is bizarre.
I mean, I'm actually shook to my very core here
about what is this.
I was surprised by his reaction in the cabinet room
where he was sitting next to Pam Bondi
and the reporter asked Pam Bondi about the Epstein file.
And then the president interrupting and saying,
you don't have to answer that if you don't want to.
Do you want to answer that?
And then he says to the reporter,
why are you still asking these questions about Epstein?
That creep has been dead for years.
Well, it was the president that raised this during the campaign.
It was the president who said he was going to get to the bottom of it
and was going to release all the information.
I mean, five months ago,
they had the press conference with the files saying part two is coming.
That's right.
Just release it.
It's as simple as that.
And him saying to the reporter,
we were just talking about dead kids in Texas.
You just desecrated them.
I mean, it was just desperate.
Don't ask questions.
Well, anybody knows.
I was surprised.
So looking at that fear, I mean, he said,
oh, the Democrats had the file.
I think I've talked to sources.
That's what it is.
They took some of the Jane Does that were fake.
You know, when they were first targeting Trump,
they knew he was going to run.
They started surveilling him.
That's been released 2013.
I was part of the same deal.
NSA files that release leaked to us.
But the point is, is that I believe Trump,
they would have already released it to burning before.
I've never seen any of the MO that he was involved with.
Plus, he's not the type that would go compromise himself
even if he was in the kids, which he's done.
Obviously, not in Russia getting pissed on.
That's ridiculous, too.
The same people.
So it makes sense that they're only to put the file
what embarrasses him.
Probably, you know, some FBI reports.
So then he has to do a special counsel.
He has to bring it out and meet it head on
instead of acting like he's running scared.
And I've never seen Trump run scared like this.
I think that's the way to say it.
I don't say this to hurt Trump.
I have to tell the truth.
I'm seeing running scared behavior.
And then I ask myself, OK, then what is it?
I wonder if he's been threatened.
I wonder if the Democrats have something
that maybe they made up out of whole cloth.
I mean, my God, we're all afraid of what A.I.
can do these days and deep fakes
and all of this this kind of thing.
So I wonder if if he would just rather this go away
even at the expense of of having guilty people
go free or not be prosecuted.
Just because he doesn't want to have to fight a fight
that is going to be that is going to be made up
and almost logical.
They didn't want him to use this against them.
So they drop a dime on themselves,
which we actually put out a Bo Boyle scrape.
And he said, I got a call from my New York guy.
They've got it all.
We're going to get to Bonnie tomorrow and we broke it.
But obviously, whatever they leave in New York
and then let Trump know they have and then he gets it
and doesn't want any.
Oh, my God, we're not releasing this.
It's a new rush gate.
It's all fake.
I think he's told us that this is a setup
and I actually believe him.
But that argues then for the appointment
of a special counsel because then the special counsel
can do the forensic investigation
and say the president's right.
This is all fake.
All right, do five more minutes.
We got to go to break.
John, I got to have you on for 10 hours.
We got to do commercial free podcasts.
Sometimes those are huge as well.
John Kiriakou.
JohnKiriakou.com real fast.
You've written so many books.
If you recommend one book to people, what is it?
I think it's my second book.
It's called Doing Time Like a Spy.
How the CIA taught me to survive and thrive in prison.
What you got for exposing torture.
Hey, thank you, Barack Obama.
Yes.
Well, a nice person.
And is he an Arabist?
I'll ask you that question when I come back.
But first, ladies and gentlemen.